东伦敦
-=TLF字幕组=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
翻译  不再的华年
翻译  筱宸葭
校对  诸星龟龟
时间轴  筱宸葭
统筹  饭离烨
特效  筱宸葭
CIA伦敦分局
实时追踪进展如何？
Where are we on real-time tracking?
正从英国人头顶的一个卫星上建立后门程序
Backdooring off a satellite the Brits have overhead.
嘿，凯特，友情提示
Hey, Kate, friendly reminder.
这周末你走之前
I'm gonna need your passcodes
我需要你的
and decryption keys before you clear out
密码和解密密钥
at the end of the week.
嗯，我会记得的
Right. I'm not gonna forget.
对了，玛丽安娜
Oh, Mariana
外面发生什么事了？
what's going on out there?
得到线索说有个重要嫌犯出现在了伦敦
Got a tip that a high-value suspect is here in London.
总统也在这里，这两件事是不是有什么联系？
Is it connected to the president being here?
据推测是的
That's the speculation.
确认目标身份
Positive I.D. on the target.
距南墙30英尺
30 feet from the south wall.
开始行动
Here we go.
目标在逃！
The target's on the run!
上，上，上，一小队！
Go, go, go, Team One!
是他
It's him
杰克·鲍尔
Jack Bauer.
好吧，他已经放倒了米勒，拿了米勒的武器
All right, he's taken Miller out. Has his weapon.
阿姆斯特朗，科特勒
Armstrong, Cutler
他往你们的方向去了
he's coming your way.
持续追踪中
Continuing pursuit.
他会往屋顶跑，那里是最好的逃跑路径
He'll head for the roof. That's the best way out.
鲍尔在快速移动！他要往外面跑！
Bauer's on the move! He's heading outside!
没道理啊
Well, that doesn't make sense.
凯特，拜托？
Kate, please?
别挡道！让开！让开！
Get out of the way! Move! Move!
该死！让开，让开！
Damn it! Move, move!
目标向西方移动，他要去河边
Target is moving west, on his way to the river.
跪下！双手抱头
On your knees! Hands behind your head.
我们抓到他了
We got him.
反恐24小时
第九季 第1集
以下事件发生在
上午11:06 至中午12:00 之间
事件实时发生
基弗·萨瑟兰
伊冯娜
斯特拉霍夫
泰特·多诺万
首相在向议会施压
The prime minister is putting pressure on Parliament
玛丽·莱恩·莱杰斯库
希望能延长他们的租期
to extend their lease
但是投票结果胜负难判
but the vote is too close to call.
人们对于我们在定点暗杀问题上
People are just not comfortable
威廉·德韦恩
使用无人机监视，感到很不舒服
with our using drones for targeted assassinations.
总统阁下？
Mr. President?
格本加·阿金纳格贝
我在想我不能怪他们
I'm thinking I don't blame them,
关于无人机我也觉得很不舒服
I'm uncomfortable with the drones, also.
但是事实无情，我们所做的就是我们的工作
The ugly truth is, what we're doing is working.
贾尔斯·马特蒂
更坏的情况下，如果我们失去了这个基地
Worse-case scenario, if we lose the base
我们还有新的选择吗？
do we have anything new?
目前为止，该地区没有任何国家
No other country in the region is willing
愿意让美国建立基地
to host an American base right now.
迈克尔·温科特
部分原因是中国人很清楚地表达了
In part because the Chinese are making it clear
他们不想我们插手该区域的事务
that they don't want us in the area.
本杰明·布拉特
他们在扩展势力范围了
And they're spreading their wings.
基姆·瑞弗
北京刚刚承认他们有个航母战斗群
Beijing just acknowledged they have a carrier group heading
正开往地中海地区，这还是有史以来第一次
for the Mediterranean. For the first time in history.
很明显这是
It's clearly intended
客 串
科林·萨尔蒙
罗斯·麦克科尔
要在租约问题上对英国人进行恐吓
to intimidate the British over the lease.
约翰·波耶加
乔瑟夫·米尔森
中国海军把它叫做“友谊之旅”
The Chinese Navy are calling it their "Friendship Tour."
这招是跟富兰克林·罗斯福学的
Taking a page from Franklin Roosevelt.
先生？
Sir?
富兰克林·德兰诺·罗斯福，他曾在20世纪初
Well, FDR, he sailed the Great White Fleet
剪 辑
乔·霍贝克
把白色舰队派往世界各地
all over the world, early 1900's
艺 术 指 导
乔纳森·李
称其为“善意之旅”
called it the "Goodwill Tour."
一样的路数
Basically the same thing.
炫耀武力罢了
Just a show of force.
我得准备一下我的演讲了，谢谢你们，先生们
I have to work on my speech. Thank you, gentlemen.
摄 影
杰弗里 C·麦咖特
音 乐
肖恩·卡勒里
谢谢
Thank you.
好的
Okay
制 作 人
伊恩·史密斯
总统阁下？
Uh, Mr. President?
监 制
布莱恩·格雷泽
那个是
It was, um
那个是西奥多·罗斯福
it was Theodore Roosevelt.
谁？
Who?
监 制
基弗·萨瑟兰
您刚才说，富兰克林·罗斯福
You said Franklin Roosevelt sailed
把白色舰队派往世界各地
the Great White Fleet around the world.
那个是泰迪（西奥多·罗斯福总统的昵称）
It was, it was Teddy.
哦，谢谢你，马克
Well, thank you, Mark.
等你不当我办公厅主任的时候
When you're retire as my chief of staff
你可以去参加 开心辞典啦！
you're gonna have a real place on Jeopardy!
监 制
强·卡萨
大卫·弗瑞
不许为我担心
Don't worry about me.
这是命令
That's an order.
是的，先生
Yes, sir.
监 制
罗伯特·科克伦
曼尼·科托
监 制
伊万·卡茨
稍等下，长官
Give me a second. Sir.
有个CIA本地分局的局长给你打来
You have a call from a local CIA Head of Station.
监 制
霍华德·高登
他说是什么事了吗？
He say what it was about?
没有
He didn't.
我是马克·布德罗
This is Mark Boudreau.
史蒂夫·纳瓦罗，先生
Steve Navarro, sir.
编 剧
乔尔·苏尔诺
罗伯特·科克伦
我们局刚抓到了一个人
My station just apprehended a man
多个机构都在通缉他
with a multi-agency warrant issued against him.
编 剧
伊万·卡茨
曼尼·科托
你们是这些机构中最首要的
You're at the top of the alert list.
他是谁？
Who is he?
杰克·鲍尔
Jack Bauer.
导 演
强·卡萨
你确定？
Are you sure?
我确定，先生
Yes, sir.
在哪里抓到他的？
Where was he caught?
伦敦市中心东南20公里的
The old Chatham and Dominion factory 20 kilometers
老的查塔姆和自治领工厂
southeast of Central London.
这不会是巧合
It can't be a coincidence.
我也这么认为
I agree.
杰克·鲍尔是一个叛国者，也是一个精神病患
Jack Bauer is a traitor and a psychopath
他杀害了两名俄国外交官
who killed two Russian diplomats
还差点暗杀了他们的总统
and came close to assassinating their president.
这么多年之后，海勒总统出现在伦敦
And now after all these years, he surfaces in London
他也同时出现在伦敦？
the same time as President Heller?
我们不得不考虑他来这里是要伤害总统的
We have to consider the possibility that he is here
这个可能性
to do the president harm
而且还可能有其他人牵扯进来
and there may be other people involved.
我立刻对他进行审讯，查明真相
I'll be interrogating him shortly, and find out.
我们没有时间让你进行审讯了
We don't have time for the interrogations you'll conduct.
我了解到现场有特勤人员
I understand there are special activities people on site.
是的，他们在我们内部就有一个小队
Well, they have a unit inside our facility
但是他们独立运作
but they operate under a separate charter.
从不互相分享信息和犯人
We don't share intel or prisoners with each other.
但是我可以通过正式渠道
But I can have him formally
把他转移到他们的监管下对吧？
transferred into their custody?
是的，先生
Yes, sir.
很好，我立刻着手办这件事
Great. I'll get started on that. Send me over
你把鲍尔的案件卷宗发给我
Bauer's case file and keep his presence there
另外不要外泄他的存在，感谢你
on a need-to-know basis. Thank you.
我们这边也不能让任何人发现鲍尔已经出现了
No one finds out Bauer's surfaced on our end either
你明白吗？
do you understand?
那总统呢，长官？
What about the president, sir?
我说了任何人
I said no one.
嘿
Hey.
恭喜你抓到鲍尔
Congratulations on apprehending Bauer.
那可是大功一件
That's a big one.
失去你让我很不高兴，凯特
I hate to lose you, Kate.
那不公平，而且也不是你的错
It's not fair and it's not your fault.
我会让你回来的
I'll let you get back to it.
他为什么没有到屋顶去？
Why didn't he go to the roof?
什么？
What?
鲍尔，我们的人进去的时候
Bauer. He could have gone to the roof
他本可以跑到屋顶
when our men were moving in.
从屋顶他就能到达那条街上的任何其他建筑
And from there, he would've made it to any of the other buildings
这样他就能逃掉了
on the block and he'd have gotten away.
他没去很没道理
It doesn't make any sense.
也许他没有侦查好逃跑路线
Maybe he didn't scout out an escape route.
鲍尔在逃四年没有被抓住
Bauer stayed off the grid for the last four years.
他不可能这么粗心
He didn't do that by being careless.
他一定在耍什么花招
He's up to something.
反对无人机
皇家空军基地
美国空军基地
下海福特
英国下海福特
早上好
Good morning.
好不了多久，谢泼德少校
Not for long. Major Shepherd wants you
让你一来就给他打电话
to call him as soon as you arrive.
语气很不爽
Sounded pissed.
关于什么的？
About what?
没说
Didn't say.
当前用户：丹纳
用户登录：克里斯·坦纳
身份验证中
身份确认-已登录
无人机停留在19000英尺高空
Drone holding at 19,000 feet
速度80节
80 knots.
谢泼德那边祝你好运
Good luck with Shepherd.
谢谢
Thanks.
卡加克省
阿富汗
不好意思
Excuse me.
长官，我是坦纳中尉
Sir, it's Lieutenant Tanner.
你知道你的任务是
You knew your mission was to fly cover
在我护送英国军官到他们部队时进行空中掩护
while I escorted British officers to their unit.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
但是你却没有告知他们的空军总部
Yet, you didn't notify their air command.
长官，您的命令中并无此项
Sir, that wasn't in your orders.
不需要有
Shouldn't have to be.
进行授权
Get it authorized.
马上办
Right away.
又一次失职
Yet another dereliction of duty.
你就留守基地等通知吧
You're on base until further notice.
长官，我有一个周末外出的
Sir, I...have a weekend pass.
我和我妻子
My wife and I
你的外出取消
The pass is revoked.
王八蛋
Bastard.
把那份文件给办公厅主任
Get that file to the chief of staff.
安排鲍尔进行审讯
And set Bauer up in interrogation.
我以为这件事是特勤组来处理的
But I thought special activities was gonna handle that.
我想要看看在他被移交出去之前
I want to see what I can get out of him
我能问出什么来
before that transfer comes through
天知道那些人会对他做些什么
and those people do God knows what to him.
押他去审讯
Walk him down to interrogation.
干得好，埃里克
Good grab, Erik.
谢谢
Thanks.
我想看一下布拉格的
I'd like to take a look at the original intercept
那份原始情报
from Prague, the one
就是让我们发现鲍尔位置的情报
that gave us Bauer's location.
为什么？
Why?
我只是想确定一下我们没有漏掉什么事情
I just want to make sure that we're not missing anything.
就像你认为鲍尔会跑到屋顶上
Like you thinking Bauer would head for the roof
但他却没有这样的事情吗？
when he didn't?
我就，我就扫一眼就行
I just, I just want to take a quick look.
不准许你看
You're not cleared for that.
瞧
Take a look.
长官？
Sir?
怎么？
Yeah?
我觉得您应该知道这事
Uh, I thought you should know
凯特在问关于鲍尔的原始情报的事
Kate was asking about the Bauer op.
她想要看那份帮助我们抓到他的情报
She wanted to see the intercept that helped us catch him.
是这样吗？
Is that right?
是的，但我没给她看
Yeah, but I didn't give it to her.
我只是想确认一下您知道这事儿
I just wanted to make sure you were aware.
还有她还是会在国内进行调任吧？
And that she was still being transferred Stateside?
她本周末还是会离开
She's still leaving at the end of the week.
而你还是会得到她的工作
And you're still on track to get her job.
这可不是我问的事情
That's not even what I'm asking.
你问的就是这个
Yes, it is.
你应该向她学习
Instead of shoving her out the door
而不是拒她于千里
you should be learning from her.
她是个很好的外勤特工
She was a good field agent.
直言一句，那怎么可能？
All due respect, how could that be?
我是说，鉴于发生的这些事情？
I mean, considering what happened?
话说，作为一个新来的
You know, you have a lot of strong opinions
你还真是固执己见
for someone who just got here.
我只是就事论事
I'm just telling it like it is.
我的意思是，他自己的丈夫
I mean, her own husband
向中国出卖机密？
selling secrets to the Chinese?
而她不知道？
And she didn't know?
她比任何人都清楚
And no one knows that better than her
所以在她走之前别再找她麻烦
so cut her some slack until she goes.
几天而已
It's just a few more days.
你能做到的，对吧？
You can manage that, right?
凯特
我爱你
嘿
Hey.
别跟埃里克一般见识
To hell with Erik.
我把情报调出来给你看
I pulled that intercept for you
但是我想先跟你说几句话
but first there's something I want to say.
你一生努力工作才来到这个地方，凯特
You've worked your whole life to get here, Kate.
你不能让他们这样对你
You can't let them do this to you.
你得反抗这次调任
You have to fight the transfer.
乔丹，我反抗了，在他们把我关起来两个月
Jordan, I did fight, for two months locked in a room
控告我参与了亚当的事情的时候我反抗了
while they accused me of being a part of what Adam did.
但你现在已经清白了
But you were cleared.
呆在这里是你应得的，凯特
You deserve to be here, Kate.
真的吗？
Do I really?
我是说，因为我觉得亚当的事恰恰证明不是这样
I mean, 'cause I think Adam proved otherwise.
给你
Here.
你看过这个了吗？
Did you look at this?
我直接给你拿过来的
I brought it straight to you.
看布拉格警方关于鲍尔的这个信息
Look at the message from Prague police about Bauer.
看到页眉了吗？
You see the header?
嗯
Yeah.
时间标记和其余的通信量
Time stamp's out of sequence
顺序不吻合
with the rest of the traffic.
也就是说这个线索并不是来自布拉格
Which means the tip couldn't have come from Prague.
这是有预谋的
That it was planted.
没错
Exactly.
我们需要找出来是谁的预谋
We need to find out by who.
好，我们得赶紧做这件事，鲍尔马上就要被转移
Well, we better do it soon. Bauer's about to be transferred
到特勤组那里了
to special activities.
到了那个鬼地方
Once he's down that rabbit hole
他可就回不来了
he's gone.
能建立基准线吗？
You able to establish a baseline?
没有一个可靠的
Not a reliable one.
他的身体数据非常稳定，这不正常
His reading's are so steady, it's unnatural.
脉搏和体温，都非常稳定
Pulse and thermal, all completely static.
让我们看看能不能把他给搅乱
Let's see if we can shake him up.
史蒂夫·纳瓦罗，分局局长
Steve Navarro, Head of Station.
听着，你审讯犯人也审讯过很多次了
Listen, you've been on my side of this plenty of times
我也就不跟你磨叽了
so I'm just gonna lay it out.
有很多的人都想让你回答
There's a long line of people who will make sure
有关你四年前犯下的罪行
that you answer for the crimes you committed four years ago.
但现在我所关心的只是
All I care about right now is to find out
你来伦敦是否为了伤害海勒总统
if you're here in London to harm President Heller.
关心这个问题的也不只我一个
And I'm not the only one who cares.
上头下了命令
There's an order coming
要把你移交给特勤部门
to transfer you to the special activities division
进行强化审讯
for enhanced interrogation.
那时他们会对你做些什么
You more than anyone know
你比谁都清楚
what they're going to do to you down there.
我知道你救过很多人的命
Now, I know how many lives you've saved.
也为国家做过很多的贡献
How much the country is in your debt.
但是他们只会看到
But they're just gonna see
一个搞砸了的人
a man who snapped.
一个疯狂报复的人
Who went on a revenge spree.
一个不顾法律和良知而大肆杀伐的人
Killing and mutilating with no regard to the law or conscience.
一个被他的国家
A man who's labeled
当作一个…一个罪犯
by his country a...a criminal.
一个恐怖分子的人
A terrorist.
所以我认为，跟我说
So, I think talking to me
是你最好的选择
is your best option.
告诉我你为什么来伦敦
Tell me why you're in London.
我就会尽我所能，阻止特勤组
And I will do everything in my power to stop special activities
对你下手
from getting their hands on you.
说吧，鲍尔先生
Come on, Mr. Bauer.
你为什么来这里？
Why are you here?
特勤组对杰克·鲍尔的转移令
Jack Bauer's being transfered down to you, here's his file.
你们组里其他人在哪里，奥布赖恩？
Where's the rest of your group, O'Brian?
去死吧！
Go to hell!
不！不！不！
No! No! No!
杰克·鲍尔
确认死亡人员名单
嘿，马克？
Hey, Mark?
嗯，亲爱的？
Yes, hon?
我差不多好了
I'm almost ready.
嘿，我的珠宝盒在那儿吗？
Hey, is my jewelry box in there?
在
Yeah.
拿到了
Got it.
哇哦
Wow.
来
Here.
你真懂我
You read my mind.
或许你不应该去招待会
Maybe you shouldn't go to the reception.
为什么？
Why?
你这么好看
Well, with you looking like that
没有人会把注意力放在政客身上了
no one's gonna pay any attention to politicians.
不，他们会被你的领带吸引的
No, they're gonna be distracted by your tie.
我的领带？
My tie?
来
Here.
我们差不多该出发了
We should probably get going.
你爸爸估计在楼下等我们呢
Your father's probably downstairs waiting for us.
他怎么样？
How's he doing?
他挺好的
He's doing good.
我听说他在你的会上犯了个错
I heard he made a mistake in your meeting.
嗯
Well
那种小错谁都会犯的
it's a mistake anyone would make.
医生说过他要过一年才会表现出症状
The doctors said he wouldn't symptomatic for another year.
不过，他们也说过
Well, they also said
压力会使他的状况恶化
that stress could exacerbate his condition.
相信我，他应对压力应对得比我还好呢
Trust me, he's handling the stress better than I am.
我不想要你担心，好吗？
I don't want you to worry, okay?
好
Okay.
进来
Come in.
鲍尔的事情有新进展
I have an update on the Bauer situation.
早上好，布德罗夫人
Good morning, Mrs. Boudreau.
来告诉你们一声
Just, uh, want to let you know
车准备好了
your car is here.
谢谢，罗恩
Thanks, Ron.
我们在楼下等你
We'll see you downstairs.
好，我马上下来
Okay, I'll be right down.
抱歉，长官
Sorry, sir.
说吧
Talk to me.
已经下达转移命令了
The transfer order's been processed.
会尽快把鲍尔交给特勤组
Special activity should have Bauer shortly.
我在想他们从鲍尔那
I'm thinking about what happens next
得到信息后，下一步怎么办
after they get what they can from Bauer.
我想会审判他
Well, I imagine he goes on trial.
对国家而言这没什么好处
That may not be the best thing for this country.
还有其他选择吗？
Is there an alternative?
可以让他消失
He could disappear.
俄国人一直想要鲍尔的人头
The Russians have wanted Bauer's head
因为鲍尔杀了他们的人
since he murdered their people.
我要你想方设法
I want you to explore the possibility
把鲍尔交到他们手里
of handing him over to them.
要保密
Clandestinely.
总统可能会察觉
The president should be made aware.
总统已经够忙了
The president has enough on his mind.
你当时不在场
Look, you weren't there.
你不知道鲍尔对那一家的所作所为
You don't know what Bauer did to that family;
对奥德莉做过什么
what he did to Audrey.
她当时死气沉沉
She was lifeless
完全没有反应
she was unresponsive
要接受精神病治疗
under psychiatric care
没指望能康复
not expected to recover.
真想不到
I had no idea.
我陪伴了她三年
I stood by her for three years.
握住她的手，我爱着她
I held her hand, I loved her
我想她恢复过来
and I want her back.
在她有生之年
As long as she lives
她永远不会听到杰克·鲍尔这个名字
she'll never hear the name Jack Bauer.
明白
Understood.
照我说的去办
Just get me what I need.
停止无人机攻击
停止无人机杀戮
杰克，我能这么叫你吗？
Jack  can I call you Jack?
你很快就没得选了
Your options are running out fast.
转移命令马上就来了
That transfer order is coming through.
到那时，我没法帮你了
After that, I can't help you.
或者
Or
我可以安排你和你女儿见面
I can arrange it so that you can see your daughter again.
你知道金又生了个小孩吗？
Did you know that Kim had another baby?
是男孩
A boy.
鲍尔的情报有新进展吗？
Any update on the Bauer intercept?
有
Actually, yeah.
情报来自
The intercept originated
当地一家网吧
from a local Internet cafe
就在街对面
just on the other side of town.
核查网吧的监控录像了吗？
Did you check the cafe for surveillance cameras?
有监控，看这里
Snake eyes on that, but look here.
网吧，看到了吗？
The cafe, see where it is?
距离我们抓住鲍尔的地方三个街区
That's three blocks from where we got Bauer.
发送情报的人一定知道我们的程序
Whoever planted that intercept had to know our comm protocols
知道鲍尔的藏身之处
and where Bauer was hiding.
没几个人知道这个
That's a pretty short list.
我只知道一个人
Yeah, I only know one person on it.
如果这是鲍尔自己发的信息呢？
What if Bauer sent the message himself?
他为什么要发信息让自己被抓？
Why would he plant a tip he knew would get himself caught?
我们必须调查清楚
That's what we need to find out.
你去哪？
Where you going?
告诉纳瓦罗
Navarro needs to know.
你干什么？
What are you doing?
我有事跟你说
I need to talk to you.
很重要
It's important.
最好很重要
This better be good.
截获鲍尔藏身之处的情报
The intercept that gave us Bauer's location
不是来自布拉格警方
it didn't come from Prague police.
等等，你怎么知道这件事？
Back up. How do you know about the intercept?
是有预谋的
It was planted.
情报来源离我们抓住鲍尔的地方
It originated just three blocks
只有三个街区
from where we grabbed Bauer.
我想可能是鲍尔事先计划好的
I think Bauer may have planted it himself.
你是说鲍尔故意被我们抓住？
So you're saying that Bauer wanted us to catch him?
正好可以解释抓捕他时
Which explains why he didn't go to the roof
他没有往屋顶逃
during the operation.
他没想过逃跑
He wasn't trying to get away
而是希望被抓
he was trying to get caught.
情报可能是任何希望
That intercept could've been sent by anyone
抓住鲍尔的人发的
who wanted to catch Bauer.
我们必须盘问他
We need to ask him about it.
如果我们没错，他可能会开口
If we're right, maybe he'll open up.
打扰一下，长官
Excuse me, sir.
转移命令
The transfer order.
就这样吧，凯特
Well, that's it, Kate.
现在归特勤组管了
It's now in special activities' hands.
长官，我们不能放他走
Sir, we can't just let this go.
叫埃里克过来，让他负责转移的事情
Get Erik over here. I want him to take care of the transfer,got it?
好的
Yes, sir.
凯特
Kate!
妈的，把门打开！
Damn it! Get that door open!
布拉格的情报是你发送的，对吗？
That tip from Prague was sent by you, wasn't it?
你故意被抓住
You arranged to be caught.
你想混进这里来
You wanted to be brought here to this facility.
你是为了什么事，或者什么人
You're after something or someone.
看来是为了什么人
It's someone, isn't it?
是谁？
Who?
Who is it?
是谁？
凯特！
Kate!
凯特
Kate
马上出去
get out of here right now.
图表一直是平稳状态
Look, he is flat the entire session
但当我问到他故意放出情报
but when I hit him about faking the intercept
想让自己被抓时，出现了波动
and wanting to be caught, he spikes.
出去
Let's go.
有反应 说明我说的没错
It's a reaction. It's means I'm onto something.
凯特
Kate!
鲍尔被抓事出有因，我们得查清楚
Bauer is here for a reason and we need to find out what it is
查出他有什么计划
and what he's planning on doing.
这和鲍尔无关，而是亚当
This isn't about Bauer, this is about Adam.
亚当？
Adam?
你丈夫背叛了国家，背叛了你
Your husband betrayed his country and he betrayed you
你是想把气发在鲍尔身上
and now you're transferring your frustration onto Bauer.
根本不是这样的
That's not what this is about.
相信我，我明白你的感受
Believe me, I understand how you feel.
亚当是我朋友，他也背叛了我
Adam was my friend. He betrayed me, too.
你在对我进行心理分析，而不是听取
You're psychoanalyzing me instead of listening
凯特，就此打住
Kate  let it go.
如果把鲍尔交给特勤组
If Bauer's going to special activities
我敢打赌
then it's a damned good bet
这正中鲍尔下怀
that's exactly where he wants to be.
知道吗？
You know what?
不用等周末了
Forget finishing out the week.
你现在就走
You're leaving now.
护送她离开
Escort her out of here.
你的私人物品稍后给你
I'll send your personal effects later.
你要是不管
You ignore this
就是置整栋大楼于危险之中
and you're putting the entire building in danger.
鲍尔是暴力罪犯
Bauer is a violent criminal.
凯特，我真的很想帮你
Kate, I really am trying to help you.
这是最好的选择
It's for the best.
乔丹，是我
Jordan, it's me.
你在哪？我刚听说
Where are you? I just heard
纳瓦罗让人护送你离开
Navarro was having you escorted out of the building.
我要你查查这里和杰克·鲍尔
Listen, I need you to find out if anyone in this building has
打过交道的人
a prior history with Jack Bauer.
员工、被扣押者，任何人
Personnel, detainees, anybody.
好，我会反复核对
Okay, I'm running the cross-check.
有消息我打给你
I'll call you if I find something.
好的，谢谢
Okay, thanks.
以前训练时研究过你执行的任务
Used to study your missions back in training.
你很有本事，鲍尔
You were really something, Bauer.
那是以前
Back in the day.
迪恩，是我
Dean, it's me.
马上就来
I'll be right there.
中断时间：3秒钟
带我去找她
Take me to her now.
等等
Hold on.
你知道我是谁
You know who I am.
胆敢按警报，我就打爆你的头
Trigger an alarm, and I'll blow your head off.
把门打开
Now open the door.
这是你干的？
Did you do this to her?
你什么没做过
It's nothing you haven't done.
克罗伊，醒醒
Come on. Chloe, wake up.
妈的
Damn it.
放松，没事，没事
Easy. It's all right. It's all right. Okay.
杰克，你怎么来了？
Jack, what are you doing here?
我们先出去
We got to get out of here.
走吧
Come on. We gotta move.
你猜对了
You were right about Bauer.
他确实和被特勤组
He does have a connection with someone
关押的人有关系
being held by special activities.
别问我怎么进入他们系统的
And please don't ask me how I got into their system.
是谁？
Who is it?
克罗伊·奥布赖恩，三位自由信息黑客之一
Chloe O'Brian. She's one of those free information hackers.
发你手机了
Sending this to your phone now.
她曾经泄露超过万份
She was responsible for releasing over 10,000
国防部机密文件
classified DOD files.
被判叛国罪
Is charged with treason.
她曾与鲍尔在反恐组共事多年
She worked with Bauer at CTU for years.
因协助鲍尔逃离美国坐牢
Served time for helping him escape the country.
妈的
Son of a bitch.
他是来救她出去的
He's here to break her out.
我在特勤组
I'm at special activities.
鲍尔不见了
Bauer's gone.
埃里克和布兰登被放倒了，不过还活着
Erik and Brandon are down but alive.
我要你启动五级封锁
Listen, I want you to initiate a level five lockdown.
以我的名义
Do it on my authority.
你没这个资格！
You don't have any authority!
照做就是！
Just do it!
怎么回事？为什么启动封锁？
What the hell is going on? Why are we on lockdown?
鲍尔试图逃跑，长官
Bauer's trying to escape, sir.
凯特在那边
Kate's down there right now.
凯特？
Kate?
启动五级封锁
挺住，克罗伊，一定能逃出去！
Come on, Chloe. You're gonna make it!
你躲在墙后面
I need you to take cover behind that wall.
这边
This way.
蹲下，蹲下
Stay down here. Stay down.
鲍尔，够了，你跑不掉的！
Bauer! You're done. You're not getting out of here!
扔掉武器！
Drop your weapon!
扔掉！
Drop it!
双手抱头
Okay, now put your hands behind your head.
快点，双手抱头
Come on. Put your hands behind your head.
快啊
Do it.
跪下
On your knees.
奥布赖恩在哪？
Where's O'Brian?
快，克罗伊
Come on, Chloe.
贝尔切克
Belcheck.
拉她一把
You got her?
好
Yeah.
快走，快走
Come on. Come on.
快点，趴下，趴下！
We gotta go. Get down! Get down!
走！
Go!
我爱这座城市
I just love this city.
可以感受历史
You can feel the history.
我了解这个表情
I know that look.
你怎么了？
What's your problem?
会议期间你说错了
The mistake you made in your meeting.
马克说没事的
Mark said it was nothing
让我不用担心
that I shouldn't worry.
发展情况比医生的预期要快得多
It's progressing a lot quicker than the doctors anticipated.
慢慢
It's terrifying,
失去自我的感觉很可怕
the thought of slowly losing yourself.
不仅仅是记忆
Not just the memories
而是全部
but all of it.
你想做什么？
What do you want to do?
现在
Right now
我希望
I want to lock up
和英国达成这份协议
this treaty with the British.
好
Okay.
什么也别跟马克说
Don't say anything to Mark.
时机成熟时我会告诉他
I'll speak to him when the time's right.
启动恢复程序
Running recovery protocols.
接通当地监控系统
It's gonna be at least 20 minutes before I can try
追查鲍尔至少需要20分钟
and access local CCTV to look for Bauer.
好吧，恢复后立即向我报告
All right, let me know as soon as we're back up.
遵命
Yes, sir.
我们已经在周边十个街区
We're laying down a search grid
开始搜寻，召回了休假的特工
starting with a ten-block perimeter, activating off-duty agents.
你们找不到他的
You're not gonna find him.
谢谢打气
Thanks for the confidence.
想想他的计划，他知道我们的程序
Look at how he planned this. He knows our protocols, he knows
了解这里的布局
the layout of this facility
他甚至知道特勤组
he even knows that special activities keeps the identity
对关押犯人保密
of their prisoners classified.
你有什么建议？让我们放弃？
So what do you suggest, we just give up?
我要特勤组手里
I want everything that
关于克罗伊·奥布赖恩的一切资料
special activities has on Chloe O'Brian.
我们找到他的同党
We track down her known associates,
然后找出她的去向
we break down the intel for where she might go.
不是“我们”
There's no "we."
你已经不再是这里的人了
You are not part of this station anymore.
能单独和你谈谈吗？
Can I talk to you alone, please?
长官
Sir
确保当地消防部门和警方执行我们的安全协议
Make sure local fire and police follow our security protocols.
如果他们找麻烦
And if they give you
提醒他们我们有领事职权
any trouble, remind them we've got consular status.
长官
Sir
去办吧
Do it.
看看杰克做的这一切，他来这才多久？
Look at what Jack did, and he was here for how long?
我们必须找到他，交给我
Look, we need to find him. So let me do it.
让我复职吧
Put me back in the field.
你要知道
You have to understand
很多人都盯着我
I am under a microscope here, all right?
总统的办公厅主任
The president's chief of staff
为鲍尔的事向我施压
is already all over me about Bauer.
我是抓他回来的最佳人选
And I'm your best shot at getting him back.
没错，亚当是叛国者，我错过了
Look, yes, Adam was a traitor, and I missed it
这次我不想错过，我是唯一
but I didn't miss this. I'm the only one
预料到此事的人，我揣摩出了鲍尔的想法
who saw it coming. I got inside Bauer's head.
没人能办到，埃里克不能
Nobody else did that. Not Erik
你也不能
and not even you.
你认为办公厅主任揪着你不放
And if you think the chief of staff is up your ass right now
想想要是他知道有人警告过你
imagine what he's gonna do when he finds out
而你却置之不理会怎么样？
that you had a heads up on this and you dismissed it.
凯特，你在威胁我？
Kate, are you threatening me?
我可以办到，我可以找到鲍尔
I can do this, okay? I can find Bauer.
我求你交给我去办
I'm asking you to let me.
贝尔切克，在这条街尾停车
Belcheck, pull over at the end of the block.
克罗伊，克罗伊，看着我
Chloe, Chloe, look at me.
你没事吧？
Are you all right?
没事
Yeah.
那就好，我们得抓紧时间
Okay, good, 'cause we need to move fast.
手机拿着，至少一个小时内安全
Take this phone. It's gonna be secure for at least an hour.
他们一定会追踪我，我们得分开
They're gonna mobilize after me, so we need to separate.
你有安全的去处吗？
Can you get somewhere safe?
克罗伊？！
Chloe?!
你有安全的去处吗？
Can you get somewhere safe?
有
I think so.
很好，一旦我安全后
Okay, good. I will find you
我会打你这只电话
on that cell phone as soon as I'm secure.
我们得走了，快走
Now we gotta go, okay? Now come on.
能收到她手机
You got a signal from the transmitter
发射的信号吗？
that we put in her phone?
是的，我还是觉得你该直接请她帮忙
Yes. I still think you should have just asked her to help.
我害怕她不答应
I couldn't take the chance she'd say no.
你说过她是你朋友
I thought you said she was your friend.
我没有任何朋友
I don't have any friends.
走吧
Let's go.
阿富汗
D-11-3，天使五号，一切安全
D-11-3, angels five, all clear.
任务完成，执行下一步
Mission complete. Moving on to next assignment.
向南前进
Turning south.
等等，怎么回事？
Wait. What? What is this?
等等
Wait.
地狱导弹就绪
不好，不好
Oh, no, no!
武器系统
天啊
My God.
谢泼德少校
Major Shepherd.
长官，马上离开车辆！
Sir, you need to get away from that vehicle!
你们被锁定了！
You're being targeted!
你说什么？被谁锁定了？
What are you talking about? Targeted by who?
地狱导弹就绪
我的无人机被什么控制了！
Something's taking control of my drone!
导弹已被装填准备发射！
It's armed a missile to attack!
我也不明白怎么回事，长官
I don't understand it either, sir
你们得马上找掩护！
but you need to get to cover right now!
地狱导弹就绪
发射
找掩护，长官！
Get to cover now, sir!
长官，快躲开，快躲开！
Sir, move, move!
不，不！
No! No!
目标已摧毁
反对无人机
搞定了
It's done.
更多原创翻译字幕请访问
TLF论坛：http://bbs.eastgame.org
TLF中文字幕站：http://sub.eastgame.org
TLF字幕组微博：http://weibo.com/tlfsubs